When you're a person like me, you are fortified.
You are somebody who seems to always have it together.
Even when things are falling apart,
you somehow manage to keep things from bursting at the seams.
This ends up working against you
because people seem to always think that you don't need them.
People seem to always think that you are invincible,
that you are impervious to harm.
And we already know that there is something about this
that is applied to Black women in general.
But even in the personal space,
there seems to be this thing where folks really just think,
I don't need assistance.
I don't need to be embraced.
And so often, I am embracing myself.